ANKAN ROY

Kolkata West Bengal • +91 8768204119 • social8ankanroy@gmail.com https://linktr.ee/usrbincat

SUMMARY

I'm a Full-stack Developer specializing in front-end design and accessibility. I'm passionate about working quickly and efficiently, always aiming to improve and iterate. I've built a full-stack distributed system that made \$1K (80K INR) in monthly recurring revenue. I also enjoy contributing to open source projects and have made significant contributions to repositories like Podman, Containers and Http-rs.

work experience

Cashcowlabs.io, Full Stack

Jun 2024 - Present

- Created a unified distributed system for internal sass that combines different workflows into a single board. We used Redis, BullMQ, Nextjs, Express, NextAuth & Supabase PostgreSQL.
- Streamlined project workflows, enhancing overall efficiency by 125%
- Used renderer.com native load balancing solution to auto scale as needed

Figuro.in, Frontend & Marketing

Mar 2024 - Jun 2024

- Designed the Landing page using Nextjs & Figma
- Setup system to monitor customer conversion (Click Rate)
- Collaborated with the founder to work on their sass product
- Worked with marketing to develop workflow, for lead generation using "Beautiful Soup"

Cashcowlabs.io, Frontend

Jan 2024 - March 2024

- Developed the Landing page using Nextis
- A solid 15% rise in conversion, due to increase in customer trust.
- Collaborated closely with the founders to identify the key conversion drivers, enabling us to focus our efforts on enhancing these critical metrics.

PROJECTS

- *ui.figuro.in* A Collection of component build to extend the popular shadon collection.are build to be accessible and responsive. Build using Nextjs, Tailwind CSS, and Shadon.
- magic block Chrome extension designed to combat distractions in a unique manner (https://github.com/cu8code/magic-blocker) Build using Plasmo, React, Vite, Tailwind CSS and Nodejs
- Code runner Run code C, C++, Python code online (https://code-runner-tau.vercel.app/) Build using Docker, Nextjs, Node and Express

ACHIEVEMENTS

- · 1st Place at CodeRodio
- 2nd at UEMK Hack Challange
- Revived UEMK Code Club developer award

EDUCATION